import { StaticImageData } from "next/image";

import cover1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project1/cover.webp";
import cover10 from "@/assets/images/projects/project10/cover.webp";
import cover11 from "@/assets/images/projects/project11/cover.webp";
import cover12 from "@/assets/images/projects/project12/cover.webp";
import cover13 from "@/assets/images/projects/project13/cover.webp";
import cover14 from "@/assets/images/projects/project14/cover.webp";
import cover15 from "@/assets/images/projects/project15/cover.webp";
import cover16 from "@/assets/images/projects/project16/cover.webp";
import cover17 from "@/assets/images/projects/project17/cover.webp";
import cover18 from "@/assets/images/projects/project18/cover.webp";
import cover19 from "@/assets/images/projects/project19/cover.webp";
import cover2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project2/cover.webp";
import cover21 from "@/assets/images/projects/project21/cover.webp";
import cover22 from "@/assets/images/projects/project22/cover.webp";
import cover23 from "@/assets/images/projects/project23/cover.webp";
import cover24 from "@/assets/images/projects/project24/cover.webp";
import cover25 from "@/assets/images/projects/project25/cover.webp";
import cover3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project3/cover.webp";
import cover4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project4/cover.webp";
import cover5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project5/cover.webp";
import cover6 from "@/assets/images/projects/project6/cover.webp";
import cover7 from "@/assets/images/projects/project7/cover.webp";
import cover8 from "@/assets/images/projects/project8/cover.webp";
import cover9 from "@/assets/images/projects/project9/cover.webp";
import cover20 from "@/assets/images/projects/project20/cover.webp";
import cover26 from "@/assets/images/projects/project26/cover.webp";
import cover27 from "../../../../public/mockups/home.webp";

import firstProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project1/snippet1.webp";
import firstProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project1/snippet2.webp";
import firstProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project1/snippet3.webp";
import firstProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project1/snippet4.webp";
import firstProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project1/snippet5.webp";

import secondProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project2/snippet1.webp";
import secondProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project2/snippet2.webp";
import secondProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project2/snippet3.webp";
import secondProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project2/snippet4.webp";
import secondProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project2/snippet5.webp";

import thirdProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project3/snippet1.webp";
import thirdProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project3/snippet2.webp";
import thirdProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project3/snippet3.webp";
import thirdProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project3/snippet4.webp";
import thirdProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project3/snippet5.webp";

import fourthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project4/snippet1.webp";
import fourthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project4/snippet2.webp";
import fourthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project4/snippet3.webp";
import fourthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project4/snippet4.webp";
import fourthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project4/snippet5.webp";

import fifthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project5/snippet1.webp";
import fifthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project5/snippet2.webp";
import fifthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project5/snippet3.webp";
import fifthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project5/snippet4.webp";
import fifthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project5/snippet5.webp";

import sixthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project6/snippet1.webp";
import sixthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project6/snippet2.webp";
import sixthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project6/snippet3.webp";
import sixthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project6/snippet4.webp";
import sixthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project6/snippet5.webp";

import seventhProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project7/snippet1.webp";
import seventhProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project7/snippet2.webp";
import seventhProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project7/snippet3.webp";
import seventhProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project7/snippet4.webp";
import seventhProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project7/snippet5.webp";

import eighthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project8/snippet1.webp";
import eighthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project8/snippet2.webp";
import eighthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project8/snippet3.webp";
import eighthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project8/snippet4.webp";
import eighthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project8/snippet5.webp";

import ninthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project9/snippet1.webp";
import ninthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project9/snippet2.webp";
import ninthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project9/snippet3.webp";
import ninthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project9/snippet4.webp";
import ninthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project9/snippet5.webp";

import tenthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project10/snippet1.webp";
import tenthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project10/snippet2.webp";
import tenthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project10/snippet3.webp";
import tenthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project10/snippet4.webp";
import tenthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project10/snippet5.webp";

import eleventhProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project11/snippet1.webp";
import eleventhProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project11/snippet2.webp";
import eleventhProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project11/snippet3.webp";
import eleventhProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project11/snippet4.webp";
import eleventhProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project11/snippet5.webp";

import twelfthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project12/snippet1.webp";
import twelfthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project12/snippet2.webp";
import twelfthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project12/snippet3.webp";
import twelfthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project12/snippet4.webp";
import twelfthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project12/snippet5.webp";

import thirteenthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project13/snippet1.webp";
import thirteenthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project13/snippet2.webp";
import thirteenthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project13/snippet3.webp";
import thirteenthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project13/snippet4.webp";
import thirteenthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project13/snippet5.webp";

import fourteenthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project14/snippet1.webp";
import fourteenthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project14/snippet2.webp";
import fourteenthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project14/snippet3.webp";
import fourteenthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project14/snippet4.webp";
import fourteenthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project14/snippet5.webp";

import fifteenthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project15/snippet1.webp";
import fifteenthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project15/snippet2.webp";
import fifteenthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project15/snippet3.webp";
import fifteenthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project15/snippet4.webp";
import fifteenthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project15/snippet5.webp";

import sixteenthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project16/snippet1.webp";
import sixteenthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project16/snippet2.webp";
import sixteenthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project16/snippet3.webp";
import sixteenthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project16/snippet4.webp";
import sixteenthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project16/snippet5.webp";

import seventeenthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project17/snippet1.webp";
import seventeenthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project17/snippet2.webp";
import seventeenthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project17/snippet3.webp";
import seventeenthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project17/snippet4.webp";
import seventeenthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project17/snippet5.webp";

import eighteenthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project18/snippet1.webp";
import eighteenthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project18/snippet2.webp";
import eighteenthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project18/snippet3.webp";
import eighteenthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project18/snippet4.webp";
import eighteenthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project18/snippet5.webp";

import nineteenthProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project19/snippet1.webp";
import nineteenthProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project19/snippet2.webp";
import nineteenthProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project19/snippet3.webp";
import nineteenthProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project19/snippet4.webp";
import nineteenthProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project19/snippet5.webp";

import twentyProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project20/snippet1.webp";
import twentyProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project20/snippet2.webp";
import twentyProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project20/snippet3.webp";
import twentyProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project20/snippet4.webp";
import twentyProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project20/snippet5.webp";

import twentyOneProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project21/snippet1.webp";
import twentyOneProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project21/snippet2.webp";
import twentyOneProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project21/snippet3.webp";
import twentyOneProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project21/snippet4.webp";
import twentyOneProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project21/snippet5.webp";

import twentyTwoProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project22/snippet1.webp";
import twentyTwoProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project22/snippet2.webp";
import twentyTwoProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project22/snippet3.webp";
import twentyTwoProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project22/snippet4.webp";
import twentyTwoProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project22/snippet5.webp";

import twentyThreeProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project23/snippet1.webp";
import twentyThreeProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project23/snippet2.webp";
import twentyThreeProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project23/snippet3.webp";
import twentyThreeProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project23/snippet4.webp";
import twentyThreeProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project23/snippet5.webp";

import twentyFourProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project24/snippet1.webp";
import twentyFourProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project24/snippet2.webp";
import twentyFourProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project24/snippet3.webp";
import twentyFourProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project24/snippet4.webp";
import twentyFourProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project24/snippet5.webp";

import twentyFiveProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project25/snippet1.webp";
import twentyFiveProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project25/snippet2.webp";
import twentyFiveProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project25/snippet3.webp";
import twentyFiveProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project25/snippet4.webp";
import twentyFiveProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project25/snippet5.webp";

import twentySixProjectSnippet1 from "@/assets/images/projects/project26/snippet1.webp";
import twentySixProjectSnippet2 from "@/assets/images/projects/project26/snippet2.webp";
import twentySixProjectSnippet3 from "@/assets/images/projects/project26/snippet3.webp";
import twentySixProjectSnippet4 from "@/assets/images/projects/project26/snippet4.webp";
import twentySixProjectSnippet5 from "@/assets/images/projects/project26/snippet5.webp";

import twentySevenProjectSnippet1 from "../../../../public/mockups/home.webp";
import twentySevenProjectSnippet2 from "../../../../public/mockups/about.webp";
import twentySevenProjectSnippet3 from "../../../../public/mockups/skills.webp";
import twentySevenProjectSnippet4 from "../../../../public/mockups/contacts.webp";
import twentySevenProjectSnippet5 from "../../../../public/mockups/projects.webp";

export interface Project {
  id?: number;
  language?: "js" | "ts" | "python";
  development?: "backend" | "frontend" | "data" | "cli" | "other";
  type?: "test" | "commercial" | "individual" | "team";
  name: string;
  categories: string[] | null;
  image: StaticImageData;
  url?: string;
  features?: string[];
  problem?: string;
  solution?: string;
  onClick?: () => void;
  links?: {
    website?: string | null;
    github?: string;
  };
  content?: {
    description?: string;
    image1?: StaticImageData;
    image2?: StaticImageData;
    image3?: StaticImageData;
    image4?: StaticImageData;
    image5?: StaticImageData;
  };
}

export const projectsEnglishLang: Project[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "commercial",
    name: "IMConsulting",
    categories: ["Business project", "js", "Next", "Tailwind css"],
    image: cover1,
    url: "i-m-consulting",
    features: [
      "App router",
      "Responsive design",
      "Parallax effect",
      "And more...",
    ],
    problem: "Attracting clients",
    solution:
      "Creating a website with an attractive interface, easy navigation and promotion of targeted actions",
    links: {
      website: "https://im-consulting.vercel.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/SoftRyzen-internship/IM-CONSULTING",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Website for business trainer and coach Illy Mushkovsky",
      image1: firstProjectSnippet1,
      image2: firstProjectSnippet5,
      image3: firstProjectSnippet3,
      image4: firstProjectSnippet4,
      image5: firstProjectSnippet2,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "test",
    name: "Carp Travel",
    categories: ["ts", "Next", "Tailwind css"],
    image: cover3,
    url: "carp-travel",
    features: [
      "Possibility to supports many languages",
      "Responsive design",
      "Different sliders",
      "And more...",
    ],
    problem: "The company need modern and unique website",
    solution: "I create a functional one",
    links: {
      website: "https://test-soft-ryzen.vercel.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/test-soft-ryzen",
    },
    content: {
      description: "A modern and nice adaptive website",
      image1: thirdProjectSnippet1,
      image2: thirdProjectSnippet2,
      image3: thirdProjectSnippet3,
      image4: thirdProjectSnippet4,
      image5: thirdProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Norway",
    categories: ["ts", "React", "Vite", "scss"],
    image: cover19,
    url: "norway",
    features: ["Responsive design", "GoogleMaps", "And much more..."],
    problem: "Company that provide travel services need a website",
    solution:
      "I can make based on design and implement functionality according to technical requirements for projects of any complexity",
    links: {
      website: "https://norway-website.netlify.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/norway",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "This website was created for practice and improvement of frontend development after completing the courses",
      image1: nineteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: nineteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: nineteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: nineteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: nineteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "GoGreen",
    categories: ["ts", "React", "Vite", "scss"],
    image: cover18,
    url: "go-green",
    features: ["Responsive design", "And much more..."],
    problem: "Companies that create nature protected program need a website",
    solution:
      "I can create projects of any complexity based on provided requirements",
    links: {
      website: "https://go-green-website.netlify.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/go-green",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "This website was created in a few days for practice and improvement of frontend development after completing the courses",
      image1: eighteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: eighteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: eighteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: eighteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: eighteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "commercial",
    name: "4.5.0",
    categories: ["Social project", "ts", "Next", "scss"],
    image: cover2,
    url: "4-5-0",
    features: [
      "Admin panel",
      "Sign in",
      "Sign out",
      "Landing website",
      "Responsive design",
      "Different sliders",
      "And more...",
    ],
    problem:
      "Now during the war in Ukraine there are many organizations that help people - one of them is 4.5.0, which requires a website to work more efficiently",
    solution:
      "Our website solves this problem - there is introductory information about the organization, a form for registering for the issuance of humanitarian aid, and also a payment system is connected for those who want to help the organization and make donations",
    links: {
      website: "https://450-kherson-humanitarian-landing-page.vercel.app",
      github:
        "https://github.com/baza-trainee/450-kherson-humanitarian-landing-page",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Website for a public organization '4.5.0'",
      image1: secondProjectSnippet1,
      image2: secondProjectSnippet2,
      image3: secondProjectSnippet3,
      image4: secondProjectSnippet4,
      image5: secondProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Cinema search",
    categories: ["js", "React", "styled-components"],
    image: cover7,
    url: "cinema-search",
    features: [
      "Responsive design",
      "Advanced search",
      "Infinite scroll",
      "And more...",
    ],
    problem:
      "All people love to watch movies - but it’s also interesting to know what the movie is about, genre, rating, cast. Therefore, there is a need for a convenient website with search and necessary information about films",
    solution:
      "The 'Cinema search' application is beautiful, convenient and has detailed information about each movie in the search",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/movie-app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/movie-app",
    },
    content: {
      description: "SPA with routing",
      image1: seventhProjectSnippet1,
      image2: seventhProjectSnippet2,
      image3: seventhProjectSnippet3,
      image4: seventhProjectSnippet4,
      image5: seventhProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Photo app",
    categories: ["js", "React Native", "Redux", "Firebase"],
    image: cover5,
    url: "photo-app",
    features: [
      "Create an account",
      "Sign in",
      "Sign out",
      "Responsive design",
      "Infinite scroll",
      "Create post / comment",
      "Add / monitor / delete likes",
      "Edit user information",
      "And more...",
    ],
    problem:
      "We all love to share our photos with society - you can create a special mobile application for this",
    solution: "'Photo app' is exactly what is needed for this",
    links: {
      website:
        "https://expo.dev/@nastia0109/EXAMPLE?serviceType=classic&distribution=expo-go&release-channel=expamle-app",
      github:
        "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/photo-network_first-react-native-individual-project",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "An application where you can: - register, enter and exit the application; - change your avatar and nickname; - download and delete your posts or comments on them; - see other users' posts, add comments and likes to them; - open the location where the post was made; - share your cool photos! )",
      image1: fifthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: fifthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: fifthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: fifthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: fifthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "team",
    name: "IceCream",
    categories: ["js", "scss", "html", "Parcel"],
    image: cover8,
    url: "ice-cream",
    features: ["Responsive design", "And more..."],
    problem:
      "A company producing and selling ice cream needed a beautiful information website and its products",
    solution:
      "A team of novice student developers from the course took on the implementation of an adaptive website, which they successfully completed",
    links: {
      website: "https://margomarm.github.io/team-project-icecream/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/team-project-icecream",
    },
    content: {
      description: "IceCream website",
      image1: eighthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: eighthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: eighthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: eighthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: eighthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "team",
    name: "News",
    categories: ["js", "scss", "html"],
    image: cover6,
    url: "news",
    features: [
      "Advanced search",
      "Responsive design",
      "Light / Dark mode",
      "Pagination",
      "New York Times API",
      "And more...",
    ],
    problem:
      "Everyone reads the news and needs a convenient website to easily find, track what they read, save and delete articles they like",
    solution:
      "The News site is very convenient and has all the necessary functionality",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/news-team-project/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/news-team-project",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Very convenient 'News' website ",
      image1: sixthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: sixthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: sixthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: sixthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: sixthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "My blog",
    categories: ["js", "css", "scss", "html"],
    image: cover10,
    url: "my-blog",
    features: ["Responsive design", "And more..."],
    problem: "I always wanted to have my own website",
    solution:
      "First, before taking the courses, I created my own website for practice",
    links: {
      website: "https://Anastasia-front.github.io/My-blog/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/My-blog",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "This is my own adaptive website where I collected all the information about myself ( this project can be considered a portfolio of my starting works )",
      image1: tenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: tenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: tenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: tenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: tenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "FoodDX",
    categories: ["html", "css", "scss", "js"],
    image: cover16,
    url: "food-dx",
    features: ["Responsive design", "And much more..."],
    problem:
      "Companies that create delicious and aesthetically pleasing food need a website",
    solution:
      "I can design and code projects of any complexity based on provided layouts",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/Food-website/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/Food-website",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "This website was created in a few days after completing the first block of my studies to reinforce the material learned ( I made several changes after the initial commit to improve the work )",
      image1: sixteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: sixteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: sixteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: sixteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: sixteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "team",
    name: "Task Pro ( frontend )",
    categories: ["js", "React", "Redux", "css"],
    image: cover4,
    url: "task-pro-frontend",
    features: [
      "Frontend",
      "Backend",
      "Create an account",
      "Sign in",
      "Sign out",
      "Responsive design",
      "Create boards / columns / tasks",
      "Edit user / board / column / task information",
      "Delete user / board / column / task information",
      "Drag & drop",
      "Email support ",
      "And more...",
    ],
    problem:
      "People often need to plan their lives in different areas of activity - there is a reason to create an appropriate application that solves this need",
    solution: "The application 'Task Pro' is just a scheduler",
    links: {
      website: "https://tkachenko01001.github.io/project-REACT_NODE/",
      github: "https://github.com/Tkachenko01001/project-REACT_NODE",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Application-scheduler",
      image1: fourthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: fourthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: fourthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: fourthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: fourthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "PhoneBook App",
    categories: ["js", "React", "mui", "styled-components"],
    image: cover11,
    url: "phonebook-app",
    features: [
      "Create an account",
      "Sign in",
      "Sign out",
      "Responsive design",
      "Add / delete / edit contacts",
      "And more...",
    ],
    problem:
      "Everyone needs to store their contacts somewhere - so you need to create a convenient application for this",
    solution:
      "PhoneBook App copes well with the task of a phone book like in phones",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/phonebook-app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/phonebook-app",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "Contact book application with asynchronous operations and user authorization",
      image1: eleventhProjectSnippet1,
      image2: eleventhProjectSnippet2,
      image3: eleventhProjectSnippet3,
      image4: eleventhProjectSnippet4,
      image5: eleventhProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "WebStudio",
    categories: ["html", "css", "scss", "js"],
    image: cover17,
    url: "web-studio",
    features: ["Responsive design", "And much more..."],
    problem:
      "The first homework assignment for frontend development courses needed to be completed",
    solution: "I completed it twice as fast as the deadlines required",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/web-studio/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/web-studio",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "I created this website during the first block of my studies ( managed it quite well from the beginning )",
      image1: seventeenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: seventeenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: seventeenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: seventeenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: seventeenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "test",
    name: "First test",
    categories: ["js", "React", "Redux", "styled-components"],
    image: cover12,
    url: "first-test",
    features: ["Responsive design", "And more..."],
    problem:
      "There was an assignment to do a test from the course in 5 days, but I found out about it late and completed it in 10 hours",
    solution:
      "All points from the technical specifications were implemented ( including additional ones )",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/first-tech-test/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/first-tech-test",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "Create tweet cards and add interactivity at the click of a button + pagination, routing, tweet filtering",
      image1: twelfthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twelfthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twelfthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twelfthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twelfthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Website for Instagram",
    categories: ["ts", "React", "scss", "Parcel"],
    image: cover9,
    url: "website-for-instagram",
    features: ["Responsive design", "Parallax effect", "And more..."],
    problem:
      "I needed a site where all my links to social networking pages and the necessary resources for contacting me were collected",
    solution: "I have created a corresponding website",
    links: {
      website: "https://instagram-header-link.netlify.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/instagram-link",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Website for links and contact me",
      image1: ninthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: ninthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: ninthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: ninthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: ninthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },{
    id: 27,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Portfolio",
    categories: ["ts", "Next.js", "scss", "next-intl","next-themes"],
    image: cover27,
    url: "portfolio",
    features: ["Responsive design", "Parallax effect", "And much more..."],
    problem:
      "I needed a site where all my projects, skills and information about me were collected in one place",
    solution: "I have created a corresponding website",
    links: {
      website: "https://portfolio-anastasia-front.vercel.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/portfolio",
    },
    content: {
      description: "My own website",
      image1: twentySevenProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentySevenProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentySevenProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentySevenProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentySevenProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    language: "js",
    development: "cli",
    type: "individual",
    name: "CLI",
    categories: ["js", "Node", "Nodemon", "Yargs"],
    image: cover13,
    url: "cli",
    features: ["Command line interface"],
    problem: "There was a need to create CLI",
    solution: "This is the first homework of backend in courses",
    links: {
      website: "",
      github:
        "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/first-acquaintance-with-node.js",
    },
    content: {
      description: "CLI ( Command line interface ) application",
      image1: thirteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: thirteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: thirteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: thirteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: thirteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    language: "js",
    development: "backend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "REST API",
    categories: ["js", "Node", "Mongoose", "Express"],
    image: cover14,
    url: "rest-api",
    features: ["Contacts backend"],
    problem:
      "There is a need to create a phone book application and you need REST API",
    solution: "This project fits this need perfectly",
    links: {
      website: "https://contacts-backend-eikd.onrender.com",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/nodejs-first-rest-api",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Backend for a phone book application",
      image1: fourteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: fourteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: fourteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: fourteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: fourteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    language: "js",
    development: "backend",
    type: "team",
    name: "Task Pro ( backend )",
    categories: ["js", "Node", "Mongoose", "Express"],
    image: cover15,
    url: "task-pro-backend",
    features: [
      "cors",
      "dotenv",
      "jwt",
      "mongodb",
      "mongoose",
      "rest-api",
      "nodemon",
      "joi",
      "bcrypt",
      "cloudinary",
      "multer",
      "nodemailer",
      "cross-env",
      "query-string",
      "swagger-ui-express",
    ],
    problem:
      "On the final team project at the end of the courses, there were two sub-teams - frontend and backend. I was the team lead of the backend development team and led the general presentation on defense",
    solution: "Our sub-team perfectly coped with the assigned tasks",
    links: {
      website: "https://project-react-node-back.onrender.com",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/project-REACT_NODE_BACK",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Backend for a Task Pro application",
      image1: fifteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: fifteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: fifteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: fifteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: fifteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    language: "python",
    development: "other",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Python Start",
    categories: ["The beginning of learning a programming language"],
    image: cover20,
    url: "python-start",
    features: [
      "functions",
      "recursion",
      "data-structures",
      "data-types",
      "regular-expressions",
      "loops-and-iterations",
      "conditional-statements",
    ],
    problem:
      "There was a need to help my husband with his studies - since he worked a lot and he needed support - and while I was on maternity leave with the baby, I simultaneously, not forgetting web development, began to take various courses in Python in order to also master the knowledge of analyst data and data scientist",
    solution:
      "As a result, I took many courses and had a good grasp of the basic concepts to get started",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-start",
    },
    content: {
      description: "First steps into Python",
      image1: twentyProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    language: "python",
    development: "cli",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Staff",
    categories: ["Python", "CLI", "serializing", "OOP"],
    image: cover21,
    url: "python-staff",
    features: ["serializing", "OOP"],
    problem:
      "The existing system lacks a Command-Line Interface ( CLI ) for managing staff information efficiently. This absence limits the user's ability to interact with the staff database and perform various operations seamlessly through a command-line interface. To address this issue, implementing a CLI will enhance user experience and provide a more user-friendly way to execute commands related to staff management, such as adding positions, editing information, finding details, and more",
    solution:
      "Integrate a CLI into the staff management system that allows users to interact with the application through a command-line interface. The CLI should support a set of commands corresponding to various staff management operations, making it easier for users to input instructions and receive relevant information. This will enhance the accessibility and usability of the staff management system, providing a convenient and efficient means for users to handle staff-related tasks",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-staff",
    },
    content: {
      description: "CLI for managing staff information",
      image1: twentyOneProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyOneProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyOneProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyOneProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyOneProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    language: "python",
    development: "cli",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Bot",
    categories: ["Python", "recursion", "CLI"],
    image: cover22,
    url: "python-bot",
    features: [
      "Countries ( info, comparison )",
      "Directory structure",
      "Phone book ( add, change, get, delete )",
    ],
    problem:
      "The absence of a Command-Line Interface ( CLI ) limits the convenience and speed of user interaction with three main areas of information: 'Countries ( info, comparison ),' 'Directory structure,' and 'Phone book ( add, change, get, delete ).' Tasks related to obtaining information about countries, working with directory structures, and managing the phone book could become more convenient and efficient with a command-line interface",
    solution:
      "Implementing a command-line interface for each of the specified areas. This will provide users with the ability to perform operations quickly and conveniently, sending commands to retrieve information about countries, interact with directory structures, and perform operations related to managing the phone book, such as adding, changing, getting, and deleting contacts. A command-line interface can simplify and expedite the interaction with these functions, providing a convenient and efficient tool for users",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-bot",
    },
    content: {
      description: "CLI for getting and managing information",
      image1: twentyTwoProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyTwoProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyTwoProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyTwoProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyTwoProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    language: "python",
    development: "other",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Workbook",
    categories: ["Python", "Examples"],
    image: cover23,
    url: "python-workbook",
    features: ["The code is executing", "Formatted output in the console"],
    problem:
      "The absence of necessary information compiled in one place always slows down the coding process because one has to constantly search for method names or rules for working with specific data structures",
    solution:
      "Creating a conspectus solves this problem, and it also revisits and reinforces the material",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-workbook",
    },
    content: {
      description: "A lot of information is recorded",
      image1: twentyThreeProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyThreeProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyThreeProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyThreeProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyThreeProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    language: "python",
    development: "other",
    type: "individual",
    name: "LeetCode",
    categories: ["Python", "Tasks", "Solutions"],
    image: cover24,
    url: "python-leetcode",
    features: ["Tasks", "Solutions"],
    problem:
      "Solving tasks is crucial for proving logical and technical skills, especially when preparing for interviews. It can be challenging, requiring a deep understanding of coding concepts and problem-solving techniques",
    solution:
      "Regularly solving coding tasks not only enhances logical thinking and technical proficiency but also provides valuable preparation for interviews",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-leetcode",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Solving tasks",
      image1: twentyFourProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyFourProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyFourProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyFourProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyFourProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    language: "python",
    development: "data",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Data Science",
    categories: ["Python", "Data Science"],
    image: cover25,
    url: "data-science",
    features: ["Tasks", "Solutions"],
    problem:
      "Solving tasks is crucial for proving logical and technical skills, especially when preparing for interviews. It can be challenging, requiring a deep understanding of coding concepts and problem-solving techniques",
    solution:
      "Regularly solving different tasks not only enhances logical thinking and technical proficiency but also provides valuable preparation for interviews",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/data-science",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Solving tasks",
      image1: twentyFiveProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyFiveProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyFiveProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyFiveProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyFiveProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    language: "js",
    development: "other",
    type: "individual",
    name: "LeetCode",
    categories: ["JS", "Tasks", "Solutions"],
    image: cover26,
    url: "js-leetcode",
    features: ["Tasks", "Solutions"],
    problem:
      "Solving tasks is crucial for proving logical and technical skills, especially when preparing for interviews. It can be challenging, requiring a deep understanding of coding concepts and problem-solving techniques",
    solution:
      "Regularly solving different tasks not only enhances logical thinking and technical proficiency but also provides valuable preparation for interviews",
     links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/javaScript-leetcode",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Solving tasks",
      image1: twentySixProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentySixProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentySixProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentySixProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentySixProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
];

export const projectsUkrainianLang: Project[] = [
  {
    id: 1,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "commercial",
    name: "IMConsulting",
    categories: ["Бізнес-проєкт", "js", "Next", "Tailwind css"],
    image: cover1,
    url: "i-m-consulting",
    features: [
      "Роутер додатку",
      "Адаптивний дизайн",
      "Паралакс-ефект",
      "І багато іншого...",
    ],
    problem: "Привертання клієнтів",
    solution:
      "Створення веб-сайту з привабливим інтерфейсом, зручною навігацією та долючення користувачів до цільових дій",
    links: {
      website: "https://im-consulting.vercel.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/SoftRyzen-internship/IM-CONSULTING",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Сайт для бізнес-тренера та коуча Іллі Мушковського",
      image1: firstProjectSnippet1,
      image2: firstProjectSnippet5,
      image3: firstProjectSnippet3,
      image4: firstProjectSnippet4,
      image5: firstProjectSnippet2,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "test",
    name: "Carp Travel",
    categories: ["ts", "Next", "Tailwind css"],
    image: cover3,
    url: "carp-travel",
    features: [
      "Можлива підтримка багатьох мов",
      "Адаптивний дизайн",
      "Різні слайдери",
      "Та багато іншого...",
    ],
    problem: "Компанія потребує сучасного та унікального веб-сайту",
    solution: "Я створила функціональний веб-сайт",
    links: {
      website: "https://test-soft-ryzen.vercel.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/test-soft-ryzen",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Гарний та сучасний фдаптивний веб-сайт",
      image1: thirdProjectSnippet1,
      image2: thirdProjectSnippet2,
      image3: thirdProjectSnippet3,
      image4: thirdProjectSnippet4,
      image5: thirdProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Norway",
    categories: ["ts", "React", "Vite", "scss"],
    image: cover19,
    url: "norway",
    features: ["Адаптивний дизайн", "GoogleMaps", "Та багато іншого..."],
    problem: "Компанії, що надає туристичні послуги, потрібен сайт",
    solution:
      "Я могу зверстати за макетом та впровадити фунціонал за технічними вимогами сайт будь-якої складності",
    links: {
      website: "https://norway-website.netlify.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/norway",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "Це веб-сайт, який я створила для закріплення та вдосконалення знань та навичок після завершення курсів",
      image1: nineteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: nineteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: nineteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: nineteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: nineteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "GoGreen",
    categories: ["ts", "React", "Vite", "scss"],
    image: cover18,
    url: "go-green",
    features: ["Адаптивний дизайн", "Та багато іншого..."],
    problem: "Компанії з програмами захисту природи потрібен веб-сайт",
    solution: "Я могу зверстати за макетом сайт будь-якої складності",
    links: {
      website: "https://go-green-website.netlify.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/go-green",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "Це веб-сайт, який я створила за декілька днів для закріплення та вдосконалення знань та навичок після завершення курсів",
      image1: eighteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: eighteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: eighteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: eighteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: eighteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "commercial",
    name: "4.5.0",
    categories: ["Соціальний проєкт", "ts", "Next", "scss"],
    image: cover2,
    url: "4-5-0",
    features: [
      "Панель адміністратора",
      "Вхід",
      "Вихід",
      "Лендінг",
      "Адаптивний дизайн",
      "Різні слайдери",
      "Та багато іншого...",
    ],
    problem:
      "Під час війни в Україні існує багато організацій, які допомагають людям - одна з них - 4.5.0, яка потребує веб-сайту для більш ефективної роботи",
    solution:
      "Наш веб-сайт вирішує цю проблему - є повна інформація про організацію, форма для реєстрації на отримання гуманітарної допомоги, а також підключено платіжну систему для тих, хто хоче допомогти організації та здійснювати пожертви",
    links: {
      website: "https://450-kherson-humanitarian-landing-page.vercel.app",
      github:
        "https://github.com/baza-trainee/450-kherson-humanitarian-landing-page",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Веб-сайт громадської організації '4.5.0'",
      image1: secondProjectSnippet1,
      image2: secondProjectSnippet2,
      image3: secondProjectSnippet3,
      image4: secondProjectSnippet4,
      image5: secondProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Cinema search",
    categories: ["js", "React", "styled-components"],
    image: cover7,
    url: "cinema-search",
    features: [
      "Адаптивний дизайн",
      "Розширений пошук",
      "Нескінченна прокрутка",
      "Та багато іншого...",
    ],
    problem:
      "Усі люди люблять дивитися фільми, а також цікаво знати, що за фільм, його сюжет, жанр, рейтинг та акторський склад. Тому потрібен зручний веб-сайт з можливістю пошуку та необхідною інформацією про фільми",
    solution:
      "Додаток 'Cinema search' гарний, зручний та містить повну інформацію про кожний фільм у пошуку",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/movie-app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/movie-app",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Односторінковий додаток з можливістю маршрутизації",
      image1: seventhProjectSnippet1,
      image2: seventhProjectSnippet2,
      image3: seventhProjectSnippet3,
      image4: seventhProjectSnippet4,
      image5: seventhProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Photo app",
    categories: ["js", "React Native", "Redux", "Firebase"],
    image: cover5,
    url: "photo-app",
    features: [
      "Створення облікового запису",
      "Вхід",
      "Вихід",
      "Адаптивний дизайн",
      "Нескінченна прокрутка",
      "Створення повідомлення / коментаря",
      "Додавання / видалення лайків",
      "Редагування інформації користувача",
      "Та багато іншого...",
    ],
    problem:
      "Ми всі любимо ділитися своїми фотографіями з громадськістю - можна створити спеціальний мобільний додаток для цього",
    solution: "'Photo app' - саме те, що потрібно",
    links: {
      website:
        "https://expo.dev/@nastia0109/EXAMPLE?serviceType=classic&distribution=expo-go&release-channel=expamle-app",
      github:
        "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/photo-network_first-react-native-individual-project",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "Додаток, де можна: - зареєструватися, увійти та вийти з додатку; - змінити свій аватар та нікнейм; - завантажити та видалити свої дописи чи коментарі до них; - переглянути дописи інших користувачів, додавати коментарі та лайки до них; - відкрити місце, де був зроблений пост; - поділитися своїми класними фотографіями : )",
      image1: fifthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: fifthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: fifthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: fifthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: fifthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "team",
    name: "IceCream",
    categories: ["js", "scss", "html", "Parcel"],
    image: cover8,
    url: "ice-cream",
    features: ["Адаптивний дизайн", "Та багато іншого..."],
    problem:
      "Компанія, яка виробляє та продає морозиво, потребувала гарного інформаційного веб-сайту для своїх продуктів",
    solution:
      "Команда початківців студентів взяла на себе реалізацію адаптивного веб-сайту, яку успішно завершила",
    links: {
      website: "https://margomarm.github.io/team-project-icecream/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/team-project-icecream",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Веб-сайт для компанії, яка виготовляє та продає морозиво",
      image1: eighthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: eighthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: eighthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: eighthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: eighthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "team",
    name: "News",
    categories: ["js", "scss", "html"],
    image: cover6,
    url: "news",
    features: [
      "Розширений пошук",
      "Адаптивний дизайн",
      "Світла / темна тема",
      "Пагінація",
      "New York Times API",
      "Та багато іншого...",
    ],
    problem:
      "Кожен читає новини і потребує зручного веб-сайту для легкості пошуку, відстеження того, що прочитано, збереження та видалення статей, які подобаються",
    solution:
      "'News' - це дуже зручний веб-сайт з усією необхідною функціональністю",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/news-team-project/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/news-team-project",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Дуже зручний веб-сайт 'News'",
      image1: sixthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: sixthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: sixthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: sixthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: sixthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Мій блог",
    categories: ["js", "css", "scss", "html"],
    image: cover10,
    url: "my-blog",
    features: ["Адаптивний дизайн", "Та багато іншого..."],
    problem: "Я завжди хотіла мати свій власний веб-сайт",
    solution:
      "Спочатку, перш ніж почати курси, я створила власний веб-сайт для практики",
    links: {
      website: "https://Anastasia-front.github.io/My-blog/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/My-blog",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "Це мій власний адаптивний веб-сайт, де я зібрала всю інформацію про себе ( цей проєкт можна вважати портфоліо моїх початкових робіт )",
      image1: tenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: tenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: tenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: tenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: tenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "FoodDX",
    categories: ["html", "css", "scss", "js"],
    image: cover16,
    url: "food-dx",
    features: ["Адаптивний дизайн", "Та багато іншого..."],
    problem:
      "Компанії з виготовлення смачної та естетично гарної їжі потрібен веб-сайт",
    solution: "Я могу зверстати з макетом проєкт будь-якої складності",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/Food-website/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/Food-website",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "Це веб-сайт, який я створила через кілька днів після завершення першого блоку навчання, щоб закріпити пройдений матеріал ( я багато разів робила усілякі зміни після основного коміту, щоб покращити роботу )",
      image1: sixteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: sixteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: sixteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: sixteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: sixteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "team",
    name: "Task Pro ( frontend )",
    categories: ["js", "React", "Redux", "css"],
    image: cover4,
    url: "task-pro-frontend",
    features: [
      "Frontend",
      "Backend",
      "Створення облікового запису",
      "Вхід",
      "Вихід",
      "Адаптивний дизайн",
      "Створення дошок / стовпців / завдань",
      "Редагування інформації користувача / дошки / стовпця / завдання",
      "Видалення інформації користувача / дошки / стовпця / завдання",
      "Drag & drop",
      "Підтримка електронної пошти",
      "Та багато іншого...",
    ],
    problem:
      "Люди часто потребують планувати своє життя в різних сферах діяльності - є причина створити відповідний застосунок, який вирішить цю потребу",
    solution: "Додаток 'Task Pro' - це власне і є планувальник",
    links: {
      website: "https://tkachenko01001.github.io/project-REACT_NODE/",
      github: "https://github.com/Tkachenko01001/project-REACT_NODE",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Додаток-планувальник",
      image1: fourthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: fourthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: fourthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: fourthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: fourthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Додаток 'Телефонна книга'",
    categories: ["js", "React", "mui", "styled-components"],
    image: cover11,
    url: "phonebook-app",
    features: [
      "Створення облікового запису",
      "Вхід",
      "Вихід",
      "Адаптивний дизайн",
      "Додати / видалити / змінити контакти",
      "Та багато іншого...",
    ],
    problem:
      "Кожному потрібно десь зберігати свої контакти - отже, потрібно створити зручний додаток для цього",
    solution:
      "Додаток 'Телефонна книга' добре справляється з завданням телефонної книги, яка є в телефонах",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/phonebook-app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/phonebook-app",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Сайт з асинхронними операціями та авторизацією користувача",
      image1: eleventhProjectSnippet1,
      image2: eleventhProjectSnippet2,
      image3: eleventhProjectSnippet3,
      image4: eleventhProjectSnippet4,
      image5: eleventhProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "WebStudio",
    categories: ["html", "css", "scss", "js"],
    image: cover17,
    url: "web-studio",
    features: ["Адаптивний дизайн", "Та багато іншого..."],
    problem: "Треба було виконати перше домашнє завдання з верстки на курсах",
    solution: "Я його зробила у 2 рази швидше, ніж того вимагали дедлайни",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/web-studio/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/web-studio",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "Це веб-сайт, я створила на першому блоці навчання ( для початку впоралася добре )",
      image1: seventeenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: seventeenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: seventeenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: seventeenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: seventeenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    language: "js",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "test",
    name: "Перший тест",
    categories: ["js", "React", "Redux", "styled-components"],
    image: cover12,
    url: "first-test",
    features: ["Адаптивний дизайн", "Та багато іншого..."],
    problem:
      "Було завдання зробити тест на курсах протягом 5 днів, але я дізналася про нього пізно і виконала його за 10 годин",
    solution:
      "Всі пункти технічних завдань були реалізовані ( включаючи додаткові )",
    links: {
      website: "https://anastasia-front.github.io/first-tech-test/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/first-tech-test",
    },
    content: {
      description:
        "Створення карток твітів та додання інтерактивності за допомогою кнопок + пагінація, маршрутизація, фільтрація твітів",
      image1: twelfthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twelfthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twelfthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twelfthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twelfthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Сайт для Instagram",
    categories: ["ts", "React", "scss", "Parcel"],
    image: cover9,
    url: "website-for-instagram",
    features: ["Адаптивний дизайн", "Паралакс ефект", "Та багато іншого..."],
    problem:
      "Мені знадобився сайт, де були б зібрані всі мої посилання на сторінки в соціальних мережах та необхідні ресурси для зв'язку зі мною",
    solution: "Я створила відповідний веб-сайт",
    links: {
      website: "https://instagram-header-link.netlify.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/instagram-link",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Веб-сайт для посилань та зв'язку зі мною",
      image1: ninthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: ninthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: ninthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: ninthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: ninthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    language: "ts",
    development: "frontend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Portfolio",
    categories: ["ts", "Next.js", "scss", "next-intl","next-themes"],
    image: cover27,
    url: "portfolio",
    features: ["Адаптивний дизайн", "Паралакс ефект", "Та багато іншого..."],
    problem:
      "Мені потрібен був сайт, де всі мої проекти, навички та інформація про мене були б зібрані в одному місці",
    solution: "Я створила відповідний веб-сайт",
    links: {
      website: "https://portfolio-anastasia-front.vercel.app/",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/portfolio",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Мій власний веб-сайт",
      image1: twentySevenProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentySevenProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentySevenProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentySevenProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentySevenProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    language: "js",
    development: "cli",
    type: "individual",
    name: "CLI",
    categories: ["js", "Node", "Nodemon", "Yargs"],
    image: cover13,
    url: "cli",
    features: ["Інтерфейс командного рядка"],
    problem: "Була потреба створити інтерфейс командного рядка",
    solution: "Це перша домашня робота з backend на курсах",
    links: {
      website: "",
      github:
        "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/first-acquaintance-with-node.js",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Додаток інтерфейсу командного рядка ( CLI )",
      image1: thirteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: thirteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: thirteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: thirteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: thirteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    language: "js",
    development: "backend",
    type: "individual",
    name: "REST API",
    categories: ["js", "Node", "Mongoose", "Express"],
    image: cover14,
    url: "rest-api",
    features: ["Backend для телефонної книги"],
    problem: "Є потреба створити додаток телефонної книги - потрібно REST API",
    solution: "Цей проєкт ідеально підходить для цієї потреби",
    links: {
      website: "https://contacts-backend-eikd.onrender.com",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/nodejs-first-rest-api",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Backend для додатка телефонної книги",
      image1: fourteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: fourteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: fourteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: fourteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: fourteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    language: "js",
    development: "backend",
    type: "team",
    name: "Task Pro ( backend )",
    categories: ["js", "Node", "Mongoose", "Express"],
    image: cover15,
    url: "task-pro-backend",
    features: [
      "cors",
      "dotenv",
      "jwt",
      "mongodb",
      "mongoose",
      "rest-api",
      "nodemon",
      "joi",
      "bcrypt",
      "cloudinary",
      "multer",
      "nodemailer",
      "cross-env",
      "query-string",
      "swagger-ui-express",
    ],
    problem:
      "На фінальному командному проєкті при завершенні курсів було дві підкоманди - по фронтенду й бекенду. Я була тім-лідом команди розробників з бекенду й вела загальну презентацію на захисті",
    solution: "Наша підкоманда чудово впоралася із поставленими завданнями",
    links: {
      website: "https://project-react-node-back.onrender.com",
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/project-REACT_NODE_BACK",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Backend for a Task Pro application",
      image1: fifteenthProjectSnippet1,
      image2: fifteenthProjectSnippet2,
      image3: fifteenthProjectSnippet3,
      image4: fifteenthProjectSnippet4,
      image5: fifteenthProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    language: "python",
    development: "other",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Python Start",
    categories: ["Початок вивчення мови програмування"],
    image: cover20,
    url: "python-start",
    features: [
      "функції",
      "рекурсія",
      "структури даних",
      "умовні оператори",
      "типи даних",
      "регулярні вирази",
      "цикли та ітерації",
    ],
    problem:
      "There was a need to help my husband with his studies - since he worked a lot and he needed support - and while I was on maternity leave with the baby, I simultaneously, not forgetting web development, began to take various courses in Python in order to also master the knowledge of analyst data and data scientistБула потреба допомагати чоловіку з навчання - оскільки він багато працював і йому портібна була підтримка - і поки я була в декреті з немовлям я паралельно не забуваючи веб-розробку ще почала проходити різні курси по Пайтону щоб також оволодіти знаннями дата аналіста та дата вченого",
    solution:
      "Як результат я пройшла багато курсів і добре оволоділа базовими поняттями для початку",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-start",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Перші кроки в Python",
      image1: twentyProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    language: "python",
    development: "cli",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Staff",
    categories: ["Python", "CLI", "серіалізація", "ООП"],
    image: cover21,
    url: "python-staff",
    features: ["серіалізація", "ООП"],
    problem:
      "Існуюча система не має інтерфейсу командного рядка ( CLI ) для ефективного управління інформацією про персонал. Відсутність цього інтерфейсу обмежує можливості користувача взаємодіяти з базою даних персоналу та виконувати різноманітні операції зручним способом через інтерфейс командного рядка. Для вирішення цього питання імплементація інтерфейсу командного рядка дозволить покращити взаємодію користувача з системою та забезпечить більш зручний спосіб виконання команд щодо управління персоналом, таких як додавання посад, редагування інформації, пошук деталей та інше",
    solution:
      "Інтегруйте інтерфейс командного рядка в систему управління персоналом, який дозволить користувачам взаємодіяти з додатком через інтерфейс командного рядка. Цей інтерфейс повинен підтримувати набір команд, що відповідають різним операціям управління персоналом, щоб користувачам було легше вводити інструкції та отримувати відповідну інформацію. Це покращить доступність та зручність системи управління персоналом, надаючи зручний та ефективний спосіб користувачам виконувати завдання, пов'язані з персоналом",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-staff",
    },
    content: {
      description: "CLI для управління інформацією про персонал",
      image1: twentyOneProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyOneProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyOneProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyOneProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyOneProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    language: "python",
    development: "cli",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Bot",
    categories: ["Python", "рекурсія", "CLI"],
    image: cover22,
    url: "python-bot",
    features: [
      "Країни ( інформація, порівняння )",
      "Структура директорій",
      "Телефонна книга ( додавання, зміна, отримання, видалення )",
    ],
    problem:
      "Відсутність інтерфейсу командного рядка ( CLI ) обмежує зручність та швидкість взаємодії користувача з трьома основними областями інформації: 'Країни ( інформація, порівняння )', 'Структура директорій' та 'Телефонна книга (  додавання, зміна, отримання, видалення )'. Завдання, пов'язані з отриманням інформації про країни, роботою зі структурою каталогів та управлінням телефонною книгою, можуть стати більш зручними та ефективними за допомогою інтерфейсу командного рядка",
    solution:
      "Впровадження інтерфейсу командного рядка для кожної з зазначених областей. Це надасть можливість користувачам виконувати операції швидко та зручно, надсилати команди для отримання інформації про країни, взаємодіяти зі структурою каталогів та виконувати операції з управління телефонною книгою, такі як додавання, зміна, отримання та видалення контактів. Інтерфейс командного рядка може спростити та прискорити взаємодію з цими функціями, забезпечуючи зручний та ефективний інструмент для користувачів",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-bot",
    },
    content: {
      description: "CLI для отримання та управління інформацією",
      image1: twentyTwoProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyTwoProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyTwoProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyTwoProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyTwoProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    language: "python",
    development: "other",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Конспект",
    categories: ["Python", "Приклади"],
    image: cover23,
    url: "python-workbook",
    features: ["Код виконується", "Відформатований вивід у консолі"],
    problem:
      "Відсутність зібраної в одному місці потрібної інформації завжди сповільнює час написання коду, бо потрібно весь час шукати назви методів чи правила роботи з певними структурами данних",
    solution:
      "Створення конспекту вирішує цю проблему, плюс ще раз розбирається і закріплюється матеріал",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-workbook",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Занотовано багато інформації",
      image1: twentyThreeProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyThreeProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyThreeProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyThreeProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyThreeProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    language: "python",
    development: "other",
    type: "individual",
    name: "LeetCode",
    categories: ["Python", "Задачі", "Рішення"],
    image: cover24,
    url: "python-leetcode",
    features: ["Задачі", "Рішення"],
    problem:
      "Вирішення задач є важливим для демонстрації логічних та технічних навичок, особливо при підготовці до співбесід. Це може бути викликом і вимагати глибокого розуміння концепцій програмування та технік вирішення задач",
    solution:
      "Регулярне вирішення задач не лише покращує логічне мислення та технічну вправність, але й надає цінну підготовку до співбесід",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/python-leetcode",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Вирішення задач",
      image1: twentyFourProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyFourProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyFourProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyFourProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyFourProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    language: "python",
    development: "data",
    type: "individual",
    name: "Наука про дані",
    categories: ["Python", "Задачі", "Рішення"],
    image: cover25,
    url: "data-science",
    features: ["Задачі", "Рішення"],
    problem:
      "Вирішення задач є важливим для демонстрації логічних та технічних навичок, особливо при підготовці до співбесід. Це може бути викликом і вимагати глибокого розуміння концепцій програмування та технік вирішення задач",
    solution:
      "Регулярне вирішення задач не лише покращує логічне мислення та технічну вправність, але й надає цінну підготовку до співбесід",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/data-science",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Вирішення задач",
      image1: twentyFiveProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentyFiveProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentyFiveProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentyFiveProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentyFiveProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    language: "js",
    development: "other",
    type: "individual",
    name: "LeetCode",
    categories: ["JS", "Задачі", "Рішення"],
    image: cover26,
    url: "js-leetcode",
    features: ["Задачі", "Рішення"],
    problem:
      "Вирішення задач є важливим для демонстрації логічних та технічних навичок, особливо при підготовці до співбесід. Це може бути викликом і вимагати глибокого розуміння концепцій програмування та технік вирішення задач",
    solution:
      "Регулярне вирішення задач не лише покращує логічне мислення та технічну вправність, але й надає цінну підготовку до співбесід",
    links: {
      website: null,
      github: "https://github.com/Anastasia-front/javaScript-leetcode",
    },
    content: {
      description: "Вирішення задач",
      image1: twentySixProjectSnippet1,
      image2: twentySixProjectSnippet2,
      image3: twentySixProjectSnippet3,
      image4: twentySixProjectSnippet4,
      image5: twentySixProjectSnippet5,
    },
  },
];
